{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596790083","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596790080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596790668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596790667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596790861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596790861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596791245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596791245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596792720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596792720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596793374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596793374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596794148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596794148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596795241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596795241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596795928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596795928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMANE"," userResponse":" DEMANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596798370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596798370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596798593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596798593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596799036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596799036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596799880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596799880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596801082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596801082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596801996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596801996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596815436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596815435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596815496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596815496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596914874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596914873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 7e7477d0-8fe1-4c1c-b35a-55c8a2cf048b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596914942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596914942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 14b07c5b-cca9-483f-ac7a-3cd333aeefde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596921311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596921311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 14b07c5b-cca9-483f-ac7a-3cd333aeefde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596926381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596926381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 14b07c5b-cca9-483f-ac7a-3cd333aeefde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596937081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596937080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596937467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596937467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596937962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596937961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596938318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596938318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596938734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596938733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596939219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596939219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596939453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596939453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596942676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596942675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596942710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596942709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596943435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596943434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596943839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596943838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596944139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596944139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596944356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596944356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596944561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596944561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596944890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596944890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596945125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596945124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596948322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596948321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596948734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596948734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596951342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596951342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596951557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596951557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596951771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596951770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596955258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596955258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596959006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596959006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596960046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596960045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596962744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596962744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596963128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596963127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596963624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596963624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596963978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596963977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596964393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596964392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596964874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596964874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596965108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596965108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596968369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596968368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596968408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596968407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596969135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596969134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596969540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596969540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596969841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596969841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596970060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596970059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596970266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596970265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596970596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596970595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596970851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596970851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596973485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596973484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548596973584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548596973584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597157516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597157516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 84b1fb19-833b-4c9c-81be-daad4a68c4ec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597157580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597157580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" a0811006-1d2a-4ccb-9b22-8943888a6ee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597163733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597163733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" a0811006-1d2a-4ccb-9b22-8943888a6ee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597185656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597185656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" a0811006-1d2a-4ccb-9b22-8943888a6ee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597193174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597193174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" a0811006-1d2a-4ccb-9b22-8943888a6ee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597199673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597199673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" a0811006-1d2a-4ccb-9b22-8943888a6ee4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597220904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597220904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 4d65f05e-b2ad-412a-b88a-1fe95284aa80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_m_h"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597227604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597227602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 4d65f05e-b2ad-412a-b88a-1fe95284aa80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_j_h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597230452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597230451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 4d65f05e-b2ad-412a-b88a-1fe95284aa80"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_l_j_h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597251598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597251598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_m_h"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597258234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597258233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_j_h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597264862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597264862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_f_m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597272342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597272342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_f_m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597278973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597278973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_r_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597286434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597286433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_r_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597296666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597296665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_r_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597303348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597303347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_k_h"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597310014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597310013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597316656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597316655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_n_h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597323293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597323293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_f_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597330002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597330002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_y_g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597336644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597336644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_h_u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597349820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597349820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_r_h_u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597366364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597366364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" 2a7eaf6c-fd4e-4873-b0ec-bfd5adb5ba5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_r_h_u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597397572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597397572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_p-h-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597405685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597405685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_k-h-t"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597409051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597409051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_t-a-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597412238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597412237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_s-k-h"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597415621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597415621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_y-u-h"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597418713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597418713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_ch-h-y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597422595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597422595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_f-h-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597425977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597425977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_a-b-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597428778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597428778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-f-z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597432948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597432948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_k-h-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597438717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597438716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_h_k-h-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548597457855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548597457855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_164612"," gameId":" ba6e6d57-81fa-444d-b36d-8fa6944d3a30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_h_k-h-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}